Sorry.
Well, I'm not young anymore,
but you know, laughter is good.
Have a blessed day. Yes, you are welcome. Okay.
Never know when you are out.
I wasn't really comfortable with having somebody in her
house or even in my house.
'cause she's here more often than she's home.
So, um, you know, Adrian was like, that's cool
because you can be her home at Attendant.
I was like, oh, that's perfect. You know,
like I introduced the idea to her
and I'm like, mom, listen, I'm already doing A, B,
C, D, and Z for you.
So, you know, there's this program, you have the Medicaid,
I can get paid, so why not?
You know, four weeks ago I had a slight stroke.
I tried to hide it, it happened overnight,
but the next day it wasn't funny no more.
I just need help with a lot of things
and she does everything for me.
I couldn't do it with nobody else.
Older people, it's like, they don't like
to change, you know?
And to change to something
that you don't know is really hard.
Yes. CPHL, they set her up with the social daycare,
so yeah, she appreciates that.
The social daycare helped her change a lot, you know,
because it's not that she wasn't very social,
but she wasn't out as much, you know?
But now she's able to go out on her own.
She has a transportation
and everything, so she's really social now. I like that.
They call you when you don't come. It's a great program.
They found it for me.
My mother and I, we very close anyhow,
so we sh we spend a lot more time together
and, um, yeah, I get to see her more often.
I appreciate that. You know,
I love it. I love
it. Lee's program has helped a lot of people.
When did the time stop?